After a very, very long day, you are very sleepy
and you decide that it is time to go to bed, to sleep.
Then you lie down on the bed close your eyes.
And each time you feel heavier and heavier.
Each time it's harder and harder to open them.
Little by little sleep is consuming you.
And when you open your eyes again, you are in the open air.
You look up above you see the blue sky.
There is not a single cloud.
It's clear, clear.
And when you look ahead, you see everything, everything, everything is yellow.
It is yellow because of the wheat.
You are in the middle of a wheat field.
And the wheat goes up to over your head.
You are alone in the middle of a wheat field, there is nothing else around you.
Then you decide to walk a little, forward to see if you discover something.
You breathe ...
deeply and enjoy the oxygen and the pure air that is in the field, in the wheat field.
You keep walking and walking.
Your feet carry you alone.
One step, another step.
Little by little you are advancing and you are making your way in the wheat field.
When you do not want to continue walking you jump to try to see what is around you.
And in the distance, in the distance you see a house.
It is a small house that appears to have two stories and is made of gray brick with a red roof.
Next to the house there is a row of green pine trees.
All lined up and forming a path.
You decide to walk in the opposite direction to the house, to see if you find something else.
And you keep making your way through the wheat.
You only see the blue of the sky and the yellow of the wheat.
Until then you come to a clearing.
There is no more wheat, but in front of you there is a grape.
It is a huge, huge grape.
Very large, and it's green.
The grape is so large that it could perfectly be a three-story building.
You decide to explore what is in the grape and surround it.
You touch it with your hand, it has a soft texture.
You surround the grape until suddenly you come across some stairs.
You climb the stairs little by little.
One by one, counting them in your head.
One ...
Two ...
Three ...
And so on until you get to the top.
And once you have reached the top you are panting.
You stop for a moment to catch your breath and put your hands on your knees.
When you open your eyes again you see a pool of grape juice.
You take advantage and take off your shirt and jump head first into the pool of grape juice.
The grape juice is cool, cool, cool.
And since it is a hot day, after a walk it is wonderful.
You lie on the grape juice, relaxing.
And as you relax, you look up at the blue sky and see a single cloud, moving.
Slowly, with the wind that is blowing little, little, little.
You keep swimming, in the grape.
And when you're done, you go out and tie your shirt around your waist.
You leave the grape and go back to walking among the wheat.
To see what else you discover.
When you re-enter the wheat field,
the wheat under your feet creaks again with each step you take.
And after the refreshing bath that you have taken in the grape juice, it seems that it is not so hot anymore.
The sun hits your back, it hits your shoulders and hits your head.
But you no longer feel hot.
In fact now there is a gentle breeze that keeps you walking and walking and walking.
I hope that you are already asleep and that you have a sweet dream.
Do tell me what other things you can find in the wheat field.
Goodnight.